Here and There at Tufts UP022
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Here and There at Tufts
1855 -- 1909
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Class of 1909
Tufts College
UP022
1 Volumes
62 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the physical edition of Here and There at Tufts from 1907 along with digital representations of several of its pages. This is a yearbook-like publication written by students from the Class of 1909. It was dedicated to William Rollin Shipman.
Biographical / Historical
The undergraduates that graduated in 1909 would have, on average, entered Tufts College in the fall of 1905. This class is best known for the creation of the 1907 Here and There at Tufts, a year-book like publication that was dedicated to Tufts professor William Rollin Shipman.
- Here and There at Tufts, 1855 -- 1909; 1907; UP022.001; 1 Volumes; 62 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Here and There at Tufts. "Tufts has reached that point in her history where the many traditions and events of student life and activities should be suitably recorded, and we hope that this book has fulfilled these conditions." Organized by the class of 1909. Signed by Lewis Doane, Leroy James Cook and Edwin Morey.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Here and There at Tufts, 1855-08-22 -- 1909; UP022.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
    Published by the class of 1909.
    - Portraits of President Hamilton, Dean Leonard, Dean Wren, Dean Anthony, and Dean\tWilliams, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
      College presidents; College administrators; Faculty; Portraits; Hamilton, Frederick William; Leonard, Charles H.; Wren, Frank G.; Anthony, Gardner Chace; Williams, Harold; Tufts University
    - Portraits of President Ballou, President Miner, and President Capen, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
      College presidents; College administrators; Faculty; Portraits; Ballou, Hosea, 2d; Capen, Elmer Hewitt; Miner, Alonzo Ames; Tufts University
    - Illustration of the Festival at the Dedication of Tufts College, 1855-08-22; UP022.001.001.00001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
      Festivals; People; Tufts University
    - Exterior View of Packard Hall Taken From the Top of Ballou Hall, 1868; UP022.001.001.00001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Tufts University
    - The Quadrangle and an Exterior View of Miner Hall and Paige Hall, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00011 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Streets; Trees; Tufts University
    - Exterior View of Ballou Hall and Barnum Museum, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00012 (Box Volume 1)
      Academic; Buildings; Exterior views; Museums; Trees; Tufts University
    - View from the West of Barnum Musuem, Ballou Hall, and Goddard Chapel, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00013 (Box Volume 1)
      Academic; Buildings; Chapels; Exterior views; Museums; Tufts University
    - Exterior View Looking South from Ballou Hall Featuring Ellis Oval, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00015 (Box Volume 1)
      Athletic fields; Buildings; Exterior views; Trees; Tufts University
    - Exterior Views of People Walking on Streets and Images of Deserted Streets, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00016 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; People; Streets; Street lights; Trees; Tufts University
    - Exterior View of Goddard Gymnasium, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00023 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Gymnasiums; Exterior views; Tufts University
    - Exterior View of Dean Hall, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00025 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Dormitories; Exterior views; Tufts University
    - The Dive in Curtis Hall, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00031 (Box Volume 1)
      Dinners and Dining; Interior views; People; Tufts University
    - Steam Laboratory in Robinson Hall, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00034 (Box Volume 1)
      Interior views; Laboratories; Machinery; Steam; Tufts University
    - Dynamo Room in Robinson Hall, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00035 (Box Volume 1)
      Interior views; Laboratories; Machinery; Tufts University
    - Physical Laboratory in Robinson Hall, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00037 (Box Volume 1)
    - Sophmore Surveying on Boulevard Field, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00039 (Box Volume 1)
      Exterior views; People; Tufts University
    - Field Surveying with Plane Table and Transit Work, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00040 (Box Volume 1)
      Exterior views; Landscape; People; Tufts University
    - Interior View of the Machine Shop, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00043 (Box Volume 1)
      Interior views; Machinery; Tufts University
    - Drawing Room in Bromfield Pearson Building, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00044 (Box Volume 1)
      Interior views; Drawings; Tables (support furniture); Tufts University
    - Exterior View of the Chemical Laboratory located in the Research Building, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00046 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Laboratories; Tufts University
    - Interior View of the Medical Chemistry Classroom, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00048 (Box Volume 1)
      Bottles; Interior views; Laboratories; People; Tufts University
    - Tufts College Station, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00049 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Railroad stations; Tufts University
    - Exterior View of Zeta Psi House, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00050 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Fraternities; Housing; Zeta Psi
    - Exterior View of the Theta Delta Chi House, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00051 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Fraternities; Housing; Theta Delta Chi
    - Exterior View of the Delta Upsilon House, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00052 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Fraternities; Housing; Delta Upsilon
    - Exterior View of the Alpha Tau Omega House, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00054 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Fraternities; Housing; Alpha Tau Omega
    - Exterior View of the Sigma Tau Alpha House, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00055 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Fraternities; Housing; Sigma Tau Alpha
    - Exterior View of the Medical and Dental School Building, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00056 (Box Volume 1)
      Academic; Buildings; Exterior views; Schools; School of Dental Medicine; School of Medicine
    - The Dean's Office in the Medical and Dental School Building Featuring Dean Williams and and an Unidentified Person, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00057 (Box Volume 1)
      Deans; Interior views; Offices; Williams, Harold; School of Dental Medicine; School of Medicine
    - Amphitheatre in the Medical and Dental School Building, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00058 (Box Volume 1)
      Amphitheatre; Interior views; People; School of Dental Medicine; School of Medicine
    - Library in the Medical and Dental School Building, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00059 (Box Volume 1)
      Interior views; Libraries; People; School of Dental Medicine; School of Medicine
    - Physiological Laboratory in the Medical and Dental School Building, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00060 (Box Volume 1)
      Interior views; Laboratories; People; School of Dental Medicine; School of Medicine
    - Dental Infirmary in the Medical and Dental School Building, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00061 (Box Volume 1)
      Dental students; Infirmaries; Interior views; People; School of Dental Medicine; School of Medicine
    - Graduating Class of 1870, UP022.001.001.00001.00063 (Box Volume 1)
      People; Students; Tufts University
    - Glee Club, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00064; E. Chickering and Co. (Box Volume 1)
      Instruments; Men; Student activities; Glee Club
    - Glee Club Trips to New York City, New Rochelle, NY, and Norway, ME, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00065 (Box Volume 1)
      Men; Student activities; Glee Club
    - Football Squad, 1906; UP022.001.001.00001.00066 (Box Volume 1)
      Athletics; Football; Men; Students; Football
    - Baseball Team, 1906; UP022.001.001.00001.00067; Barker (Box Volume 1)
      Athletics; Baseball; Men; Students; Baseball
    - Basketball Squad, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00068 (Box Volume 1)
      Athletics; Basketball; Men; Students; Basketball
    - Track Team, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00069; E. Chickering and Co. (Box Volume 1)
      Athletics; People; Students; Track (Men's); Track
    - Fencing Team, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00070 (Box Volume 1)
      Athletics; Fencing; Men; Students; Tufts University
    - New York University and Clark Intercollegiate Debate Teams, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00071 (Box Volume 1)
      Men; Student activities; Debating Team
    - Tower Cross Society, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00072 (Box Volume 1)
      Men; Student activities; Tower Cross
    - Ivy Society, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00073 (Box Volume 1)
      Men; Student activities; Ivy Society
    - Tufts College Band, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00074 (Box Volume 1)
      Instruments; Music; Students; Tufts College
    - Commencement Ceremonies, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00075 (Box Volume 1)
      Commencement; Students; Tufts University
    - View from Ballou of the Crowd at Commencement, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00076 (Box Volume 1)
      Commencement; People; Tufts University
    - Looking from the Rostrum at Commencement, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00077 (Box Volume 1)
    - The Seniors at the Tree Excercises During Commencement, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00078 (Box Volume 1)
      Commencement; People; Students; Tufts University
    - A Section of the Audience During Commencement, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00079 (Box Volume 1)
    - The Cast of "Old Fortunatus" Featuring King Athelstane and His Court, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00081 (Box Volume 1)
      Actors; Actresses; Costumes; Plays; Tufts University
    - Cast From "Old Fortunatus" Featuring Fortune, Virtue, Vice, and Their Attendants, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00082 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Night in Goddard Gymnasium, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00083 (Box Volume 1)
      Ceremonies; Gymnasiums; Matriculation; People; Student activities; Tufts University
    - The Football Banquet in Goddard Gymnasium, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00084 (Box Volume 1)
      Banquets; Football; Gymnasiums; Students; Tufts University
    - The Bubble, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00085 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Fountains; Students; Tufts University
    - The Tufts Delegation on the Bay State, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00086 (Box Volume 1)
      Boats; Students; Tufts University
    - Class of 1909 and The College Band and Rooters in Line at Portland, UP022.001.001.00001.00087 (Box Volume 1)
      Instruments; Music; People; Students; Tufts University
    - Tufts Delegation on the Bleachers in Portland, ME, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00088 (Box Volume 1)
      Football; Games; Students; Tufts University
    - Bonfire for the Baseball Team's Victory Over Dartmouth, 1906; UP022.001.001.00001.00089 (Box Volume 1)
      Athletics; Baseball; Fires; Tufts University
    - Janitors Nicholas Dwyer and Patrick Bryne, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00090 (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Trees; Workers; Byrne, Patrick; Dwyer, Nicholas; Tufts University
    - Goddard Chapel Tower, Class of 1908, Patrick Byrne on the Academic Quad, and Ellis Oval, UP022.001.001.00001.00091 (Box Volume 1)
      Athletic fields; Chapels; Snow; Students; Towers (building divisions); Workers; Byrne, Patrick; Tufts University
    - Medford Campus, 1907; UP022.001.001.00001.00092; Stebbins, N.L. (Box Volume 1)
      Buildings; Exterior views; Railroad stations; Trees; Tufts University